dnncreative.com 2013-08-23

# DNN Creative Magazine Privacy Statement

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##### Collection of your Personal Information

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your post code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke does not read any of your private online communications.

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke and DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke family of Web sites.

##### Use of your Personal Information

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke collects and uses your personal information to operate the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web site and deliver the services you have requested. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke and its affiliates. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke, in order to determine what DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke, or the public.

##### Use of Cookies

The DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke pages, or register with DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke site or services, a cookie helps DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke services or Web sites you visit.

##### Security of your Personal Information

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

##### Changes to this Statement

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke is protecting your information.

##### Updating your Details

If any of the information that you have provided to DNN Creative Magazine for DoNetNuke changes, for example if you change your email address, name or payment details or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to support@dnncreative.com.

##### Your Consent

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Continued use of this website will signify that you agree to any such changes.

##### Contact Information

DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DNN Creative Magazine for DotNetNuke at support@dnncreative.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
